bookcab.in 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Customer Information | BookCab

This privacy policy sets out how Bookcab uses and protects any information that you give to Bookcab when you use this website. Bookcab is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Bookcab may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from March 2011.

## What we collect

Unless you register to our site or book a cab you need not to provide any personal information. We may collect the following information:

• Name  
• Contact information including mobile/landline numbers and email address.  
• Personal information such as billing address and home address.   
• Other information relevant to customer bookings, surveys and/or offers.

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

• Internal record keeping.  
• We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
• We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information, which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
• From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.  
• We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
